There once lived a king,
whose mighty empire spanned
from Moodanagudda and lasted
till the Paduvana sea.
A caring wife and children
to call as his own.
Loyal subjects to whom
their king meant everything.
A royal figure who was
friendly with one and all.
He had everything,
except for peace of mind.
He visited numerous temples and
took a dip in many holy ponds.
Despite performing various religious
rituals and worshipping his ancestors,
Sound sleep and peace
of mind evaded the King.
But why?
With that very question in
mind, the king consulted
a soothsayer seeking
answers to his predicament.
O' King, you possess everything.
However, until you find a source of strength
that will guide you like a wise uncle
unconditionally love you like a
mother, you shall not attain peace.
Where would I find it, Sir?
Go in search of it.
All alone.
The king then set off.
He visits various pilgrimage centres,
meets all kinds of spiritual guides.
But no matter where he went,
the pain in his heart found no solace.
Assuming that there was no place or power that could
give him peace, the King went to the forests.
Right in the middle of the woods,
he heard the distant sound of an anklet.
The king halted right there.
But surprisingly,
the sound doesn't frighten the King.
It reminded him of a mother’s
love and an uncle’s affection.
The king then moved in the
direction of the sound.
He is guided towards a stone, in front
of which, he surrenders his weapon.
Without the King's knowledge, his eyes teared
up and his hands joined together in reverence.
The king felt joy.
Infinite joy that had
evaded him all this while.
Like a mother hugged him.
Like an uncle caressed his head.
Right then...
I bow down as your king.
Please bestow this
Demigod to me.
I’m ready to give
you anything for it.
My dear King!
Ask us for anything,
but not our Demigod Panjurli.
So, you want me,
the Panjurli Demigod, huh?
I want nothing but you, Panjurli.
I shall come along with you.
But I belong to this village.
If I bestow you with happiness, peace and
prosperity, what will you give my people?
Whatever you ask for.
You will grant all of the land, across
which the sound of my voice traversed.
Remember, I'll be accompanied by my
Compatriot spirit, the ferocious Guliga.
Should you err, even if I forgive
you, Kshetrapala Guliga won't.
You have my word, Panjurli.
The palace is decorated and
the village is spruced up.
The King welcomed the Demigod with
inexplicable joy into his kingdom.
Since then, the King's life saw no
dearth in harmony, joy and peace.
The villagers' Demigod was
now in the lap of the King.
The King’s vast land was now
in the hands of the villagers.
From then on, the holy procession
commenced from the King’s palace.
Then why is the current Landlord
asking us to return this land?
After all this is their
land, son!
There is nothing wrong if
they ask us to return it.
But we're here to serve the
Demigods, aren't we?
Where can we go
forsaking our Gods?
Son, do you know where
we humans go wrong?
We assume that we own
everything around us.
But forget the reality of
the true owner of it all.
Once we become aware of the
truth, we can live peacefully.
I didn't come all the way from Bombay
to watch Bhootha Kola [SPIRIT WORSHIP].
I need to settle this
land issue on priority.
Do you even hear yourself?
This land was donated by our
ancestors to serve the Demigod.
Since then, our family has
been living peacefully.
That's enough!
Wasn't it given as charity back then?
Do you have the slightest
idea about its current value?
If we take it back now,
we can lead a life with dignity.
It doesn't work that way.
Asking for the land back would mean going
back on the word given to the Demigod.
You and your Demigod
can take a hike!
I'm sick of hearing
this all the time.
The performance you'll see is something
I've witnessed many times before.
This is our ancestral property.
I have as much right
over it as you do.
If you can't ask for it,
then take a step back,
I'll handle this in court.
I present you the sacred offering
and invite you to wear the gaggara.
I humbly accept your invite and seek the
permission of audiences to wear gaggara.
♪ Varaha,
the Supreme among all Gods ♪
♪ He who assumes the form of a Wild boar ♪
♪ The greatest of the Demons ♪
♪ With teeth as
hard as Diamond ♪
♪ He who protects
us like a shield ♪
♪ He who embodies the
essence of Shiva ♪
♪ The one who thrives on Earth ♪
♪ He who gives refuge to
those who believe in him ♪
♪ The one who has won the
hearts of Thousands of Gods ♪
♪ We now stand in front of
you, worshipping you ♪
O' Landlord!
It's the twilight hour, O' Landlord!
It's a practice to address
your questions in my court.
Do you have any
questions, Landlord?
Panjurli?
- Yes!
As of now, I have no questions.
I do.
What?!
This place, this
property, this land.
None of these belong
to the villagers.
Quiet. Don't talk, please.
- Fine! It's not yours either.
It's mine.
You have to ensure
it's returned to me.
That's a great question, Landlord!
I'll ensure it's
returned to you.
I'll ensure the villagers'
land is returned to you!
But can you return the peace I have
blessed you with all these years?
Listen!
Won't you be able to get it back for me?
No problem.
I know where to get my job done.
So, you will go to the Court, eh?
But I shall pronounce your
judgment on those very stairs.
The land belongs
to the villagers.
That decision will
not be made today.
A day will come in
the distant future.
It belongs to the villagers?
Is this the Demigod speaking?
Or is it the performer?
Is it the Demigod or the performer?
Let it be decided today.
If it indeed is the performer,
may you find me again.
However, if it is the Demigod...
Shiva!
KANTARA - A LEGEND
Did he really disappear?
Of course he did.
Wouldn't he have
returned otherwise?
What if he was killed?
If so,
wouldn't we have found his body?
That's right.
Do you want to see the
place where he went missing?
In the forest, a fire was ablaze
across the place he went missing in.
But the fire didn't illuminate the forest,
instead it pushed it into further darkness.
What about the Landlord?
He died vomiting blood on
the stairs of the court.
An extremely powerful Demigod.
- Of course.
But I shall pronounce your
judgment on those very stairs.
What a powerful Demigod!
- Of course.
Even today, the Demigod protects this
forest, the village and its people.
So damn powerful!
[SONG HERALDING THE COMMENCEMENT OF
KAMBALA - A TRADITIONAL BUFFALO RACE]
[WARM WELCOME TO GUDDI SUDHAKARA,
A RAY OF HOPE TO THE POOR]
Which idiot drew this?
No clue.
If you find out,
ask him to meet me.
Give me the garland!
The Landlord is here!
The chief guest of today's Kambala
festival, Devendra Suttur is here...
These garlands were
meant for the buffaloes!
Is that the Landlord?
- Yep.
Is he the son of the guy who
died vomiting blood?
Yes.
- Is he also like his father?
Not at all.
He has a heart of gold.
Get ice candy for the kids.
- What is the matter with his child?
No point talking about it.
Let’s proceed Landlord.
Since the Suttur's ancestors
are our royal family.
[LUCKY DIP - 1ST PRIZE MOTOR BIKE]
Could one get this bike for real?
- The winner surely can.
On behalf of Keradi family, we request
you to make this event a grand success.
Keradi Kambala has been a
prestigious race with...
Hope everything is ready.
- Yes it's done.
Hey look! Your wife!
Check out her glances!
Check out this Buffalo's teeth.
One look and you know
it's an experienced one.
Hello, Mr Sudhakar Shetty!
- Go on, Mr Rajiv Shetty!
Shall we call the buffaloes into the arena?
- Definitely.
Will the Kola continue?
- Why won't it?
So, who's performing?
As per tradition,
Shiva must be the one to perform.
He's an irresponsible fellow.
So, his cousin Guruva
will be performing.
Come for the Kola.
Don’t miss it.
Bring your wife, too.
We'll have a blast.
The owners of all
buffaloes please proceed...
Yes, I was sitting with your wife.
Hit me!
Rampa come! It’s getting late.
We are now witnessing Kaadubettu
Shivannaʼs buffaloes entering the field.
FORGE AHEAD!
Let’s charge!
That was awesome, Shiva!
Shiva, you beat your previous
record by two seconds!
That was splendid racing!
Will our buffalo win
at least this time?
Just win?
It will break all records!
Just wait and watch Landlord!
It doesn’t matter who wins.
They are our people after all!
Run!
Superb! Our buffaloes made it first!
[KUNDAPURA FOLKLORE]
Shiva, slow down. I’m tired.
Tired? Did you run the race?
- Give me the booze.
Pour it.
- It’s hot.
Give it I say.
I'm the one drinking.
I’m leaving.
- Already?
Mahadevanna, give me a drag.
Man, our buffaloes ran
like there's no tomorrow!
The buffaloes are running.
The buffaloes are running
with all their might.
But ironically,
the owner ends up getting the medal.
Bet 10 bucks and take home 20!
Bet 10 bucks on
Tiger Prabhakar now!
I bet 10 bucks on Tiger Prabhakar.
- I bet on Silk Smitha.
Yay! Give me the prize!
I won.
Move aside.
Shivanna, the Landlord’s buffaloes
finished six seconds later than ours.
Let’s go.
Wait.
I’ll bet on Silk Smitha again.
You won’t get her, come.
Congratulations!
Lucky you!
Shivanna,
I don’t know how to ride a bike.
On behalf of the Keradi ancestral house, we thank all
the 50 buffalo owners who participated in the event.
The third place in today's Kambala
race goes to Thumbebailu Mahesh.
He bagged it!
The second place goes to….
Kaadabettu's...
Shivanna's buffaloes.
What?
The first place in today's Kambala race
goes to Devendra Suttur’s buffaloes.
Oh finally!
Our Landlord won!
Which bas*ard said so?!
- Shiva!
If rookies turn into judge,
this is what happens!
I’ll break your leg moron!
How did he win?
You stay out of this!
I’m a big man in this village!
You think you’re the prince of
Barkur, dingbat?!
How did his buffaloes win?
- They ran. So they won. How else?!
Is the Landlord your father to award him?!
- Moron!
Dimwit, you’re the moron!
I’ll kill you scoundrel!
Is your father
judging this contest?
You slob!
You guys are destroying the
reputation of the Kambala.
You bash him, Shiva!
Come here, you Landlord’s dog!
Handle the mic with care.
It’s not your father’s!
Don’t you dare talk
about my father!
Landlord!
Smash him!
Wow! Shiva's smashing them!
Don't you see him
getting beaten up?
Whose side are you on?
- I’m on the winner’s side.
Go and thrash him!
Thrash him!
God! He's coming here!
I’m dead meat!
You wretched dog!
Let’s clean ourselves
at the pond.
The mud has entered the
unmentionable places.
Scoundrel!
When the village is together celebrating,
how dare you guys fight instead?
You wretched dog!
He started it all.
How can I keep quiet?
So? You guys just fight?
His buffaloes have been winning
for the last three years.
Heʼs one of us.
So letʼs support him.
Go bring the medal.
Dammit!
Could it be scotch?
- No clue.
Hey Shiva.
- Landlord?
If you’re pissed with me,
vent it out in front of me.
No need to do it in
front of the villagers.
Sorry, Landlord.
Things go out of
hand when I'm drunk.
Then I better be
prepared for more.
Yes!
Wait! No!
Shiva wins it consecutively
for the fourth time.
God bless!
We are all from
the same village.
We have to live in
harmony till the end.
What do you say?
- You're right.
This is for the
Kola celebrations.
Make sure it’s grand.
Let me know if it doesn't suffice.
Okay then.
What is it?
Go on. Take it.
Good Lord!
We waited all this while for this!
The Landlord is so fond of
us that he thrashed Mohan!
You should have seen his face!
Guddi looked like the cat that
swallowed the canary!
Hey Mala, Susheela!
Where are you off to?
Look at their attitude!
Where is your sister?
Look at them making faces!
Hey Rampa,
our Landlord is a good man.
He’s the only one who gives
us a party without asking.
Time for some soda!
- One for me too.
What the hell's wrong with you?!
Celebrate our victory man!
What rubbish!
Ginger?!
Don’t you have a plain one?
That's not it?!
Did I give you the ginger one ?
Yes, damn your ginger!
How much is it?
- Don’t worry, it’s on me.
Really?
You take the bike and go to Kailasa.
I’ll join you in a bit.
Hey Abbu! All good?
Yes.
Haven’t you gone to the mosque?
- You think I live there?
Shiva is bad company for my
son, Lacchu!
Hey Vasanthi akka (sister)!
Hope he doesn't lose his way.
- Move aside!
Use the horn, monkey!
- Namaskara!
Looks like it's finally yours.
- Could it be anyone else's?
Where is Lacchu?
- What?!
Did he go out hunting?
- Shiva!
Greetings uncle.
- Hey Shiva.
This is the Landlord’s
donation for the Kola.
He wants us to ask
if we need more.
Has there ever been instance
where he hasn’t given enough?
Hey Guruva!
This time too the medal is ours.
Everybody knew that you won.
Did you need this
medal to prove it?
Why should I let go of
what’s rightfully mine?
I need your blessings.
- It’s okay!
Man, he really got Mohana yesterday.
- Real bad.
Kusuma.
You stay here. I’ll come.
Why do you need medicine?
What happened?
I saw something last
night and freaked out.
What did you see?
- It was me.
I'm tired of trying to
convince him that it was me.
Well...
I wonder how many more
nightmares await him.
The fighter cock is here.
You called him useless but
he managed to get the medal.
He didn’t get it for the
race, but for wrestling.
He’s the black sheep of his
family and this village.
Hey Kapil and Deva.
There’s only one medal.
Kindly adjust.
Where’s mother?
Hasn’t she fed you yet?
It’s right here.
Eat well.
Next year,
we should break this year’s record.
If we win, I'll get two medals.
What did you hunt, Lacchu?
A hen.
A hen?
You didn’t have to hunt it.
You could’ve just caught it.
A wild hen dude.
- Where is Rampa?
Sire set off in the dawn,
asking me to wait for him.
Shivanna, when will you
teach me to ride the bike?
Rampa will train you to ride.
He is out riding right now.
Shall I go and join him?
Don’t interrupt the ride midway.
The bike may jerk to a halt!
This is for Rampa.
This too.
Let’s finish it off
before he comes.
Bulla!
Damn, he’s here!
Did you take a shower?
- I didn’t get time.
Mud on your knees?!
Did you fall off the bike?
Well...
I attempted to do this and
something else happened.
Rampanna, I heard you ride well.
I want to ride too.
Shut up and eat.
Hey, this is not boar meat!
Guys, shall we go hunting tonight?
- Yes.
Shiva! Where is that dog?
Let me get my hands on him!
I’ll thrash him!
Hey! Shivanna!
Where are you off to?
Weren't we going in
the night to hunt?
Then why did he run now?
- No clue.
Bulla, look!
Kamala is walking upside down!
Look at the stick her in hand!
- This one will hurt!
Wastrel!
Look at him hiding in that tree!
Shameless bugger!
Didn’t I tell you not
to hunt wild boars?
You’re fit for roaming
the streets like a dog!
Damn! Who told you we
hunted a wild boar?
It was a wild hen!
You shameless liar!
Kamala,
we really hunted a wild hen.
Not a wild boar.
Check if you want.
Dimwit! You stay out of this!
Had you gotten married at the right
age, you’d have had kids by now.
Would you have spoilt
them like this?
Despite your age, you have no brains!
Bloody wretch!
What can I do if you
got married at 13?
Why are you laughing?
What are you doing
with this old man?
I came to Ramappa to learn to ride!
- Kamala!
What’s the matter with you?
You think you’re a teenager?
Hope you remember we studied
together till Class 3.
I have been witnessing
your nonsense ever since.
Kamala, are you high?
What makes you speak like this?
You shut your mouth!
You, come home!
Your funeral awaits you!
I’m sick of this fellow.
What a crazy woman!
- This is exactly why I quit school!
Let’s cancel tonight’s
hunting plans.
We've to attend
your funeral, right?
Bugger off!
We hunted last night.
Haven't slept a wink.
We decided to offer it
first to you and came by.
Sir, please don’t mind.
It's a small wild boar.
Next time, we'll hunt a big one!
Irrespective of its size,
it's our duty to offer you the meat.
The Deputy Forest
Officer is here!
Sir, greetings!
- How are you doing, Raghu?
Doing well sir.
Sir please spare us!
What's that sound?
Sir, some repair work is going on.
Is the forest your
ancestral property?
Will you hunt again?!
Morons! Will you hunt again?
Murali!
Are you acting smart because
there is no RFO in this division?
At this rate, they will hunt
all the animals in the forest.
So?
If you torture people in your custody,
they will torture you outside.
This is a sensitive area.
If you don't learn to handle the
people, the road ahead looks tough.
Listen,
I donʼt eat meat on Thursday.
You can go.
So many survey stones
have been moved.
Finish the survey soon
and submit the reports.
There are three villages
left apart from Kaadubettu.
Oy! Who goes there?
Come here.
Whatʼs all this?
I'm asking you. What is this?
Different kinds of produce...
- I know that.
Do you have permission to take
all this from a reserve forest?
What for?
Every year, we take all this from
the forest for the Bhootha Kola.
Donʼt you know itʼs
an offence to do so?
Guys, today letʼs hunt
at least four wild boars.
Why? One is enough.
Letʼs go.
You can burn some calories.
Hey, forest officer! Hide!
Take the guns and come
from the other side.
Then where should we
get the produce from?
Thatʼs not my problem.
So what can we do now?
Henceforth, you have to take my permission
if you have to do anything in the forest.
Whatʼs the issue?
Shiva, this man says we need his permission
to bring produce from the forest.
Is it?
Do we have to take permission?
The government won't
spare you if you don't.
Dammit! We've been living here much before
your government came into the picture.
If you think about it,
you need our permission.
Do you have it?
Speak up.
No, right?
You don’t need any permission Vasanthiakka.
You can go.
Okay!
You guys leave!
It’s so damn hot!
Itʼs a big deal we
let you in the forest!
A map, eh?
Hey, where can I find
Parapaade on the map?
I guess you donʼt know either.
They are also searching for the same!
- Is it? Continue.
Okay, carry on!
Let me know if you find it.
Ravi. -
- Sir?
Patrol near Parapaade tonight.
- Okay sir.
Lacchu, have I told you
my grandfather's story?
Damn! There he goes again!
1850.
This was the time of the Kings.
During the reign of
King Gajendra Simha....
The King and my Grandpa Thaniya,
the brave warrior were close friends.
The King once took my
Grandpa for a hunt.
They hunted 14 wild boars in
the course of their banter.
My god!
When they went ahead,
they found another one.
A Wild boar?
- No dude. It was a tiger.
Oh!
What happened?
Shush!
- What is it Shivanna?
Hey! What is it?
I didnʼt spot anything. Did you?
I can't spot
anything but tigers.
[GUNSHOT]
Hey Shiva! What happened?
Nothing dude.
- He shot something, didnʼt he?
Letʼs search for it.
- I didnʼt see it too.
Shiva!
- We wonʼt find it. Letʼs go.
Lacchu,
where were we in the story?
The tiger was eyeing
the King as its prey.
But the King was looking
at the tiger as his prey.
He took out the gun and
pressed the trigger.
Boom!
Whatʼs that?
- Boom Boom!
What's happening?!
- The bloody gun didnʼt fire.
The tiger came
pouncing at the king.
Suddenly,
my Grandpa grabbed the Kingʼs gun.
He rammed it against the ground twice, gave it a
jerk, aimed it to the ground and took his shot.
Boom!
The gun fired and the
tiger died on the spot!
How did the tiger die if he
aimed the gun at the ground?
The bullet bounced
off and hit the tiger.
It died on the spot!
What a useless gun!
Shut up! That very gun was gifted to my
Grandpa in the grand court of the the King.
Okay dude.
Shush!
Hey stop!
Itʼs wounded. Letʼs chase it!
I heard a sound from this side.
Rampa, shoot it, idiot!
Heʼs useless!
Why did you bring him?
Iʼm not going to use
this old manʼs gun!
If you come hunting again,
Iʼll break your leg!
Fire quickly!
I canʼt fire with this gun!
Go to the other side
and shoot you moron!
Why hold a gun if you
canʼt shoot, bonehead?!
Stand away from me,
else I'll die here.
Come on.
Bloody boar!
Didnʼt I tell you?
My Grandpa's gun never
fails to bring us meat.
Look, such a big one!
It’s so huge!
Must be Bullaʼs relative.
Letʼs hunt another one.
Donʼt be an idiot!
We can't do it all over again!
One is enough. Letʼs go back.
Is this all youʼre capable of?
Okay then.
Tie it up. Letʼs go.
Didnʼt we shoot a boar here?
We won't find it. Let's go.
Let's try and look here.
Look all over and you'll
find your Grandpa's remains.
Was your grandfather buried here too?
If your mother finds out about this
hunt, she’ll thrash you.
I won’t let her beat him.
That portion of the meat
is for the Landlord.
The other portion is
for my grandpa’s gun.
Okay, cut the meat now.
Did you have your dinner?
This moron won't get it.
I'll kill you today.
Imbecile!
Did you go hunting again?
You just wonʼt listen!
What's wrong?
What happened?
Let me explain it to you in detail!
You mongrel!
Shiva, we're hungry.
Got anything to eat?
No, my mother will
give you a earful! Run!
You guys are here?!
Youʼre the one spoiling him!
Kamala, listen to me.
Rampa, come.
Dimwits! Wait for me!
Did it hurt?
- Not really.
Heʼs used to it.
Yes!
Shiva, where were you last night?
My mother was home and
is scared to sleep alone.
I went home to be with her.
Despite you caring for her so
much, she has no sympathy.
Stop at Mahadevachariʼs house.
I have some work.
Mahadevanna, How are you?
You guys carry on.
I have to get my bum repaired.
What?
- Sorry, my gun repaired.
Thimmappa, take them in.
Get the others to
unload the vehicle.
Yes, Sudhakar?
- Sir...
The thing is...
If payments keep getting delayed,
how do I get the labour folk?
Iʼm helpless too.
Since the RFO is suspended,
none of the bills are getting through.
Sir, you are doing
most of his work.
Wish you could do something
about the payment too.
Give me some time Sudhakar.
I’ll get it done.
Sir, the Landlord had invited you home.
I'd told you.
I forgot.
- I thought so.
Iʼll go.
Okay then. Iʼll take a leave.
All good?
Sir, we heard two gunshots
in the forest yesterday.
Hunting has taken place for sure.
But we didnʼt find them.
However,
we found this near Parapaade.
Whatʼs this?
The head ornament
of the Demigod.
Seems ancient.
It commands more respect
than a King’s crown.
Looks like a massive boar!
Yes. Weighs 40 kilos.
If itʼs leg weighed 40 kilos,
did the boar weigh 500 kilos?
We meant the boar
weighs 40 kilos.
Mohan, there is a bag on
the table inside. Bring it.
Okay Landlord.
One more thing.
Ensure that your land
documents are in place.
The department has
begun the survey.
Really?
Why else did I call you over?
- But they didn't inform me.
Keep quiet.
Keep the correct documents, okay?
- Okay Landlord.
Youʼve been nodding your
heads for many years now.
Our people donʼt
understand these things.
If you donʼt understand,
you must ask me.
Why the hell did
you call me here?
Calm down man! Take it easy.
If we donʼt get it.
You'll handle it, right?
Of course, Iʼm here.
Next time, see if you can
hunt something with spots!
Sure.
Let the Bhootha Kola get over.
What does he mean spotted?
A leopard?
Deer, you idiot!
Give it here.
Take it.
Hey Venkatramana, letʼs go.
Hey Jagga! Mohan!
Load the rice bags, vegetables
and fruits in the officer's jeep.
Take it.
- Pick them up.
Please come!
Whatʼs all this?
Youʼre our guest.
How can I send you
back empty-handed?
Come letʼs chat
over a cup of tea.
Hope things are going
fine in the village.
I hear youʼre set to conduct
survey in our village.
You know our people, right?
Their livelihood
depends on this forest.
They're uneducated.
I suggest you grin
and bear with it.
The previous officer was
in good terms with me.
Please ensure that we
donʼt face any troubles.
Iʼd say itʼs better if you
ensure that there is no trouble.
My work will be on.
Let me know when
there are festivals.
Iʼll come over for food.
My wife isnʼt at home.
She left me because I don't
grin and bear with things.
See you.
Sure.
Sir, this is the boundary
of the forest department.
Encroachment has been
noticed in these two regions.
This belongs to Devendra Suttur
and this to the villagers.
I have issued notice to
the concerned parties.
Sending notice to the
villagers wonʼt work.
You have to convince them.
Sir, these villagers
are a little bonkers.
If you confront them,
they pounce on you.
All government officers
say the same story.
But it shouldnʼt become the
excuse for our incompetence.
♪ What a beauty ♪
♪ In the voice of Padanna. ♪
O' priest!
O' Landlord!
What do you think lies
ahead for all of you?
Will it be the
poison or the elixir?
If it's poisonous,
let God take care of it.
If it's elixir,
let this village savour it.
Let the procession begin.
I'm elated!
♪ What a beauty? ♪
♪ Narrate the story till morning ♪
♪ Till the journey of life is over ♪
♪ Is it a story or a tale of grief? ♪
♪ It's truly a sad thing ♪
[FIREWORKS]
Whatʼs that?
Bhootha Kola has begun.
Itʼs an annual ritual
that is celebrated.
Take out the vehicle.
I heard the forest officer was
acting too smart the other day.
Had I been there,
Iʼd have slapped him!
You seem like an angry
man, aren't you?
When I get angry,
I canʼt tolerate injustice.
My body begins to...
What? Empty already?
- Yep.
Dammit! We should've got more.
Shivanna,
can you return my bike key?
Why?
Sister Leela is here.
She'll teach me
to ride the bike.
When did she come?
- Did she finish her training?
Yep. If she gets the job,
she will earn 1000 bucks a month.
What? Really?
- 1000 bucks?!
Give me a minute. Iʼll be back.
Did he fall in love
with her salary?
Thousand bucks in
a month is great.
Shiva!
- Yes?
Come here.
What?
Donʼt drink too much.
No mom. I wonʼt drink today.
Iʼll watch the whole performance.
- Let me see.
Ideally, you should
be the one performing Kola.
But youʼre so irresponsible.
Thank god! Leave me alone!
I have no plans to vanish
like her husband did.
I want to enjoy life.
- You and your enjoyment.
The Landlord is here.
I'm coming.
This is Girijakka.
- Greetings!
Hope you're doing well.
Take this.
Alright.
God bless everyone.
Shiva!
You look pretty suave, eh?!
Oy! Stop!
Hey Shiva!
Looks like you didnʼt see me!
Attention devotees!
Food offerings are being served.
Kindly go to the dining area.
Where did she go?
Move it! Iʼll serve this line.
Salad! Ivy Gourd.
Salad!
Shivanna! Leela's here.
Her training is over.
She will stay here.
- Is that so?
Nice!
- Pass the fritters.
Shivanna, thatʼs enough.
Others have to eat, too.
It's okay. Enjoy.
He's always been like that.
He is very fond of me.
Ivy Gourd salad.
Salad.
Acting cocky, huh?
Donʼt you remember me?
You might have
completed your training.
No need to get cocky with me.
♪ You shall never
win when I'm here ♪
What happened?
She pinched me!
Woah! Is he also here
for the Bhootha Kola?
Greetings sir!
Bless us, Panjurli!
- Greetings, Sir.
Hey Shiva!
Guruva dances really well.
But no one can match the
grandeur of your father!
The forest officer is here.
Dammit!
[CRACKER BURSTS]
Ay! Who asked you to burst them?
I do it every year.
Give me the bag.
- What?
What are you doing?
Heʼs already picked
a fight with Abbu.
Come, letʼs go.
Oy!
Stop!
Who asked you to take this?
Oy!
What?
Give me the bag.
Give it to me!
- Why?
I donʼt want to hear the
sound of crackers again.
What do you mean?
How can crackers be soundless?
Does your Demigod dance only
to the sound of crackers?
Looks like youʼre drunk
and blabbering nonsense.
You're crossing your limits now.
This showy spectacle of yours is
causing harm to the wild animals.
Donʼt you get it?
Showy?!
You guys heard that?
Did the wild animals drop
by and complain to you?
Ask them to file a case.
We will handle it in court.
If they do so,
will your Demigod argue on your behalf?
Whatʼs your problem?
You donʼt seem to like us.
Sundar, come back.
Wait!
You seem to have crossed your limits.
You think we'll take it?
Hey.
- Wait!
Come back!
I canʼt control my anger.
You were talking
about our Demigod.
I donʼt think you know of their power.
Should I narrate the story to you?
Somebody narrated it to your
father and he narrated it to you.
You have been roaming like a nomad
narrating that story to everyone.
You are jobless any way.
So, youʼre talking
about my father now.
If you stop us,
should we listen to you?
Looks like thereʼs some tussle going on.
Come letʼs go.
You carry on Landlord.
Iʼll join you.
Hey Abu. Give me the cracker.
[CRACKER BURSTS]
We will burst it. Every moment.
Stop us if you can.
Shiva, stop! Step back!
Whatʼs your problem?
When the Bhootha Kola is in
progress, what are you doing here?
When we burst crackers,
he acts like weʼve set his a** on fire.
Youʼre at the Kola.
Instead of taking the offerings, why
get involved in petty fights? Let’s talk
You've gone too far!
- Let's go.
Keep at it and I'll put an end to your
silly traditions and celebrations!
Try stopping us if you
have the balls to do so!
I'll make sure you don't
get out of here alive!
[COMMOTION ENSUES]
Donʼt you understand if I tell you once!
Keep quiet!
Is this the way to behave
with a government officer?
Donʼt you understand?
You please carry on sir.
Heʼs a forest officer.
Give him some respect!!
Get away!
Sir, please leave.
Donʼt act like crazy people!
- Move it.
What happened?
- He wants to stop the Bhootha Kola.
He wants to stop the Kola?
Give me a sword. Iʼll kill him!!
You shouldnʼt have
stopped me Landlord.
I shouldnʼt have?
Watch the Kola now.
What the hell man!
Did you have a nightmare?
Damn! Will this ever end?
When will you scoundrels ever
get a good night’s sleep?
The whole year you all keep roaming
like cavemen around the village!
There are times when I feel
like adding poison in your tea!
How are you able
to live this life?
Thatʼs the fun part!
Donʼt forget to have
breakfast, you wretch.
Is Shivanna home?
- Heʼs inside.
How are you Leela?
Youʼve plumped up. Nice!
Iʼll see you later.
[HUMS A SONG]
Shivanna!
What's wrong?
Did you wake up now?
Please save me!
I was the one who
pinched her last night!
Who did you pinch?
- He pinched her.
Where?
- Not sure. Could be her as*!
I need to have a word with you.
It was just a joke.
A joke?! We thought otherwise.
No, I swear I was joking.
- Itʼs okay even if it was a joke.
Iʼm happy you did
that yesterday.
Aren't you upset?
Why would I be upset?
Didnʼt I tell you I was happy?
Isnʼt it dear?
At your age,
even I did the same thing.
You have my full
support in this matter.
Thanks!
- What a useless father!
What exactly are
you referring to?
Iʼm talking about Shivanna
confronting the forest officer.
Yeah right.
What happened?
Nothing much.
I totally forgot
what I came here for.
Please tell me.
Her training is done.
Whatʼs that called?
Forest department
guard training.
Exactly! Can you speak to the Landlord
and get her a job in this village?
Is that all? Of course!
Letʼs go to the Landlord right away.
If youʼre busy, Iʼll take her.
Iʼm free!
Really? Letʼs go then.
Anyway, I have your support.
- Of course you do!
He'll be back.
Please donʼt.
We donʼt take money.
Ah! Snuff.
Dad, can he really get me the job?
Oh god!
Itʼs you!
I was wondering what poked me!
Make her sit in between.
Women's safety is of
utmost importance.
Make her sit.
Please sit dear.
Leela went for it, eh!
It should've been me
riding, right?
Greetings!
[KUNDAPURA FOLKLORE]
Landlord, greetings!
- What is it, Shiva?
This is Leela.
She's been trained as a forest guard.
What is he staring at?
This one's mine.
Help her find a job, please?
- Sure. Why not?!
It'll be done.
- I'm grateful.
♪ O’ rich ornamental beauty ♪
♪ You're a sorcerer who can
dig for gold with your sole ♪
♪ Gifted enough to blindfold
thyself like Gandhari ♪
♪ You're the cool shade
that sprinkles fond hope ♪
♪ That smile of
yours… My goodness! ♪
♪ Just like the affection
of the holy month ♪
♪ The captivating femme fatale ♪
♪ The timid spotted deer ♪
♪ The alluring
impressionable dye ♪
♪ You broke into my heart,
with just a touch of your forelock ♪
[KUNDAPURA FOLKLORE]
Bloody hell!
Power cut at a crucial moment!
Woah! The show's clearly on!
- Shiva!
Leela!
- Shiva-Leela's melody, is it?
Rampa?
- Well...
I was showing her
the crescent moon.
♪ O’ chattering flower ♪
♪ Don’t you baffle me
without a warning ♪
♪ Why must I warn you? ♪
♪ For every inch of your
body is watching me ♪
♪ Deep in my heart,
a musical is all set to be performed ♪
♪ Awaiting your
arrival at its crest ♪
♪ Our tournament of soft whispers
has turned into public broadcast ♪
♪ On the cheeks of the sunset,
the thorn of timidity has planted itself ♪
♪ The child in my
heart is now stubborn ♪
♪ Let's coddle each other ♪
♪ Every flower out there
has questions to ask ♪
♪ They’re out planting false
complaints on your shadow ♪
Want to visit the
Landlord's factory?
Come on now.
♪ Your eyes continue to
sing the chorus of passion ♪
♪ Then why brave the
efforts to dance to its tune? ♪
♪ Turning into a
whirlpool of fragrance ♪
♪ You’ve entrapped my heart ♪
♪ Tell me why you jumped the
fence in the dream I’m dreaming? ♪
♪ On the cheeks of the sunset, the
thorn of timidity has planted itself ♪
♪ The child in my
heart is now stubborn ♪
♪ Let's coddle each other ♪
♪ Beautiful surprises now
lie in front of the eyes ♪
♪ Every smooth metaphor I
had for you are now failing ♪
Hey Shivanna!
Get down here.
- Okay.
The mongrel's over there.
Thanks.
Careful.
You'll come in the
evening, right?
Raghuannna, she's one of us.
Leela! God bless.
See you Raghu Anna.
I donʼt care if it's the previous
officers' or the villagers' fault.
Today, the government
should get back the land.
Ravi, whatʼs the update?
Sir, the cops and the tahsildar
will come to the spot.
What about Sudhakar?
He said he will come with
the labourers directly.
Murali, the way you are proceeding in the
matter doesn't seem to be professional.
There seems to be a
personal agenda to this.
Whatever be the motive,
it is the government’s job, isnʼt it sir?
Donʼt carry the grudge
of the recent incident.
I trust that you will
handle this efficiently.
Yes sir.
Okay. Update me.
Thank you sir.
- Greetings sir.
Leela,
why are you standing here?
You havenʼt spoken to sir yet?
- No.
Come with me.
Sir.
- Yes?
Our new joinee, Leela.
- Sir.
The one who used
influence to get this job.
Did ironing your uniform
get you this late?
Tumbebailu, Honchukki,
Kodiargadde and Kaadabettu.
These are the places we
will be visiting today.
Much of the encroachment
is around Kaadabettu.
In a few days, they will build a few
more temples and claim the entire forest.
Ravi! Do we have his
name on the list?
No, sir.
Letʼs add it.
He will realise what it means
to have his a** on fire.
Sir, this is a sensitive matter.
Since we are dealing with
land, they might react.
Who are they to react?
Itʼs forest land.
So itʼs us who have to react.
We will have to make
them understand sir.
If it doesnʼt go right,
then we will be in trouble.
This time weʼll definitely
make them understand.
Ravi, come here.
- Sir.
Put her on night duty.
We will know how well
sheʼs been trained.
Take her along during
night patrolling.
Yes sir.
Hey Rampa!
Come and wash the buffaloes.
Now that sheʼs joined work and is
busy, you remember us.
Shut up and come.
- Am I crazy to get wet? Get lost.
Iʼll meet you later!
Have it.
Iʼm glad you didnʼt get wet!
Come now!
What the heck!
Heʼs back again!
This guy has taken
us for granted.
Where are you going?
- Iʼll be back.
Sundar,
donʼt get into a fist fight.
Officer, whatʼs the matter now?
Encroachment.
What is it?
Attachment it seems.
Attachment?
Greetings, sir.
The labourers are here.
Okay.
How come I don’t see
the usual sour faces?
Come here.
Just come!
Speak.
They're your
people, aren't they?
They would rather
listen to you than me.
Leela, whatʼs the matter?
Go stand at the back.
This is the result when you
use influence to get a job.
This is a government order.
The department has to measure
the circumference of the forest.
We will have to report
the encroachment.
Am I clear?
Sir, where is the survey stone?
Follow the officer.
Go there.
Start surveying from that stone.
Make way! Let them work.
Drag the chain to that stone.
Bring the chain this side.
What attachment are
you talking about?
Itʼs not attachment.
Itʼs encroachment.
I got that. What does it mean?
Whatʼs your name?
Attachment.
I mean.. Sundar.
Sundar, encroachment means
illegally occupied land.
Issue a notice to the concerned.
Go fast!
You were supposed to reply to the notice.
But you havenʼt.
We were busy! What now?
I know. Thatʼs why we are here.
We are peaceful people.
Just don't provoke us.
If we claim your land,
will you be okay with it?
You have done that already.
You've fenced our land.
Itʼs a one hour job.
We will shift the stones which your ancestors
and you have been moving since years.
This will not happen
as long as Iʼm alive!
Hey Sundar. Hold on.
Try stopping us.
Ay! Go back.
Once I take a step
forward, I won't step back.
On the night of Kola,
I was held back.
Are you showing off?
You donʼt have to pull
your gun for that.
I have a gun too.
It'll take time for me to bring it.
I said get back!!
Donʼt touch us!
Youʼre acting too smart.
I can fight too!
Go back, I said!
Where's Shiva?
Shivanna!
The forest officer is troubling us!
Leela, what are you doing dear?
You've joined them to
fence your own land?
Please let me do my job dad.
We don't need this
insensitive job.
Shut up people!
Go on, speak.
You guys just donʼt
respect my words.
Go on!
- Now listen.
Even I donʼt know
whatʼs happening.
Then why the hell
are you talking?!
I mean I donʼt know the
procedures involved.
Why are you pouncing
on me for that?!
After all,
he also has to perform his duty.
He'll be under pressure too.
- For what?!
Voting for you was
our biggest mistake.
Now youʼre also on his side!
No way!
Only the labourers were mine.
Iʼm on your side!
- Enough. We donʼt believe you.
We know what to do.
Come letʼs go.
Please listen to me!
Don't my words have
any value at all?
Hey, get lost!
Wait!
Donʼt disturb while marking.
Who are you to mark our land?
Thrash him right!
Sir!
Police!
Rabid dog!
Come to me! You jackas*!
I will finish you today, Bas*ard!
[GUNSHOT]
What's the big deal
about firing in the air?!
Shoot me directly if
you have the guts!
Shoot!
[GUNSHOT]
I didnʼt miss my aim.
I'm a trained officer.
Tie him up.
You have done the right
thing, sir.
Go inside!
Iʼll kick you all behind bars.
Take care.
Youʼre still wearing that
uniform, girl?
We thought you'll get
educated and help us.
But you back stabbed us.
Heʼs not eaten
anything since morning.
Shiva!
I heard you didn't
eat since morning.
Get lost!
Leela!
How dare you beat up a girl!
This was the last thing
I expected from you!
Where are you going?! Stop!
How would I know that they would ask
me to do this on the first day at work?!
None of you understand
my situation!
Annappa.
If you submit a request for the title
deed, things will move fast.
Illiterates!
Naru.
Naru, be quick.
None of your
documents are in place.
Itʼs been a while,
must have gathered dust.
Screw the dust!
I can't read a single letter.
Damn.
Who is Thukra?
Itʼs my father.
- What?
Whose document is this?
Itʼs mine.
How did his documents get
registered in your father’s name?
Both our fathers have
the same name - Thukra.
These Thukras are trouble!
Apply your thumb imprint.
Whose ration card is this?
- Itʼs mine! Abu.
You think Iʼm selling
rice, here?
What the hell?!
Tell me if youʼre
not selling rice.
Why get angry for that?
What?
- The house is beautiful.
As if he's giving rice
from his own kitchen.
I want the documents in place or else
it will be tough to argue in court.
What is it?
How dare you step in?!
You mongrel!
Hey brother, stop!!
- Moron! Iʼll kill you!
Bulla, donʼt step in.
Mohan, go mind your business!
Shiva!
- Yes Landlord?
Nothing to worry.
He is always tension free!
This is for you. Enjoy.
Please have the drink.
Landlord, what about you?
Iʼll have. You please drink.
- Okay.
Please relax.
Don't chug insane amount of alcohol just
because it's free. Watch the intake!
He hit me in front of everyone but
this Landlord too supports him.
Exactly. Are you a rabid dog
to get treated like that?
Mohan.
Every dog has its day.
We shall bite then.
You please carry on.
Iʼll be back soon.
Sir, peanuts?
I hope our land will be safe.
Why are you requesting me?
You are like our
Landlord, Shivanna.
Where do you think my land is?
Itʼs right beside the forest.
They marked my land
as encroachment.
Then?
Then I realised I didnʼt
have the right documents.
Oh!
Now?
A lawyer called Subbarao is
fighting the case since 12 years.
Someday, I might win.
Shiva!
Yes, Landlord.
We need to water the plantation.
Shall we go?
Okay.
Be quick.
- Shiva, take this.
Take the flash light.
Careful.
- Okay Ammakka.
You think they realised?
They were all in a
buzz, Landlord.
Shiva, what happened
to that match of yours?
Seen her on your bike often.
What happened to it?
We were going strong.
Until this forest officer spoilt it for us.
We broke up.
Can you get her removed from the
job, Landlord?
What can the poor girl do?
She only followed
the DRFOʼs orders.
Can you get him
removed from his post?
Itʼs not so easy Shiva.
If heʼs not performing his
duty, then we can try.
Is it so?
Then letʼs ensure he
doesnʼt perform his duty.
Besides, we have you with us.
Youʼre a smart guy Shiva!
You get things instantly!
The signal's here.
- Careful, my lord.
Come fast lady.
What happened?
What happened, Shiva?
- I saw something there. Run!
What happened?
Tell me what is it.
Hold the torch you idiot!
I can't see anything.
Take this! You can return it
if we make it out of here alive!
I was in a hurry because
her husband would return.
Shiva!
I'm going! You go home too!
Shiva! Stop!
When will you realise not to
roam the forest at such hours?
This is what you get for getting
into worthless adventures.
Don't get started.
Let him recover.
I’m advising because
you’re younger to me.
At your age, your father would visit
couple of villages to perform Kola.
Why don't you get it?
Why will he get it?
If he's busy with these wastrels,
how will he have time for anything else?
Why blame us for nothing?
Did we blind him?
I'll punch you. Shut up!
Why keep blaming
us for everything?
Let's get out.
We'll wait outside. Take care.
If you have something to
say, tell it to me.
Why blame others?
You sure get angry
for everything.
Enough now.
Let's not blow it out of proportion.
Brother, pray to the
Demigod before leaving.
Good things will come your way.
- Okay.
Alas! here comes the forest officer.
Bloody scoundrel!
Filling up the trenches marked,
doesn't make the forest theirs.
Let us wait and watch.
Boom!
Working fine, right?
Rampa get your gun repaired.
Itʼs training time.
Unlike others,
I don't miss my targets.
Carry on.
♪ The Siruras nature
is all around ♪
♪ The peacock we saw
has spread its feathers ♪
♪ In Bulpadi's lake, a boat arrived. ♪
♪ Upon which a fish had hopped. ♪
♪ Upon which a fish came and hopped. ♪
Re-telecast of today's news.
Forest Brigand Veerappan who kidnapped
forest officials in the Satyamangala forest
has warned to chop off the heads of
the officials if his demands are not.
Dammit!
Look at how evil the world is.
Nobody's as innocent as us.
- You're right.
Brother, give sir a glass of tea.
Itʼs on me.
Make sure the evil forces are
confined within the borders Guliga.
♪ A tiger lurks on the edge of the hill ♪
You said you know this region
well and asked to be posted here.
Just like the trees,
your reputation too is at stake.
♪ The wounded King tiger is growling ♪
- Canʼt you see the boar?
♪ Should it be tied
up or hunted down? ♪
Looks like hunting is on too!
♪ It's not a wild tiger
It's a pussy cat ♪
♪ Look for the thief's
footsteps and find his trail ♪
♪ Look at the twinkling
eyes in the dark. ♪
Looks like you caught
a bigger one this time.
Yes, Landlord.
It's easily 70 kilos.
You guys are freshers.
I used to hunt as a kid.
Oh! He doesn't look like a
hunter, does he?
Take this! You may leave.
I'll take your leave, Landlord.
- Sure, Thimappa.
Are you avenging the past?
You are our forest officer,
why would we seek revenge from you?!
If ever I find you troubling
the department again,
...I'll take you for a spin
on the interrogation chair.
A spin?
Gotta take that ride, eh?
We'll join you too.
Your wild animals destroy our crops.
What should we do then?
Just shoot it.
- We'll at least get meat!
Shiva, donʼt say such things.
We have a record of the number
of animals in the forest.
You better keep a tab on the
number of hunters amongst you.
If anything goes amiss,
we will get an account of it.
If thereʼs no permission to hunt,
was the license given to fire on Deepavali?
Come, letʼs talk.
Why are you running away?
Raghu Anna, a new check post?
- Yes.
Recently there's been an increase in thefts.
- Makes sense.
Good job. See you!
Okay.
♪ A snake is sleeping
in its burrow ♪
♪ Should we scare it with
a stick or feed it milk? ♪
♪ The wounded King tiger is growling ♪
♪ Should it be tied
up or hunted down? ♪
♪ That genius King has nestled
in a pit dug by himself ♪
♪ Looks like he lies hidden
and is conspiring hard ♪
♪ The Siruras nature
is all around ♪
♪ The peacock we saw
has spread its feathers ♪
Whatʼs that?
My wife said these leaves
help avoid hair fall.
Iʼll take this and leave the village.
You think this forest is
your ancestral property?
Iʼve been insulted enough times.
This time...
I wonʼt tell anyone about it.
Iʼm not lying. Try this once.
You'll get your hair back.
Is this enough?
- I don't want any, sir.
Have it. Itʼs okay.
Donʼt hesitate.
Sir, there wasnʼt enough water.
- Enough?
There wasnʼt any.
Sir, I need a favour from you.
One more peg?
Thatʼs not what I meant.
Iʼm fed up of asking the
Landlord for my payment.
If only the timber tender could
be allotted directly to me…
You don't have to do
it out of charity.
I have something for you too.
- What?
Iʼll help you capture
Shiva and his mates.
Gurnal, what was Sundar saying
about doing good to the village?
He wants revenge because
the officer hit him.
He’s hot tempered.
What a huge tree!
Were you caught cutting
down a tree like this?
It was slightly
smaller than this.
No wonder you got whacked.
Donʼt finish it all.
Keep some for me too!
We will.
You continue cutting the tree.
What a downpour sir!
Sir, please go slowly.
A pothole!
Sir, shall I drive?
Murali, letʼs go slowly.
Mr Murali…
Donʼt worry. They will be there.
I hope the information is correct.
- Absolutely sir.
Those idiots have gained a lot of headweight
from killing eating all the forest animals.
Let them taste food in jail.
That should teach them!
Bulla.
- Yes?
Iʼm sure that rabid dog will lose
his job because of this tree.
What if he doesnʼt?
- Letʼs do something bigger.
Tiger skin. Cheetah.
Do we have elephants here?
- Nope.
If so,
we could have gone for the tusk.
[WARNING SIGNALS]
I think itʼs a nightingale.
Nightingale my foot! Letʼs go.
Douse the fire!
Where are you going Shiva!
The saw is in the tree.
Whatʼs that sound?
I hear something close-by.
Looks like they
died right there.
Did you guys cut the
tree to kill him?!
God! Save us!
You messed it up big time, Shiva!
Have you lost it?
It was not intentional.
- Who will believe you?
Everyone was aware of your
feud with the first officer!
This will be considered
as a murder case!
What can we do now?
Iʼll handle this.
You know the forest well, Shiva.
Abscond for a while.
I gave them the signal.
I thought they’d follow me.
Where is Shiva?
There's no one here.
Have they left anything behind?
- Nope.
Then get down.
Because of us,
people in the jeep lost their lives.
Yes.
We tried to be over smart.
If we get caught,
weʼll be behind bars.
You guys leave.
Iʼll surrender citing
it was my fault.
Shiva!
Bas*ard!
Instead of planning what to do next,
everyone’s worried about the dead!
If you come close to
me, I'll kill you.
I'm a fierce warrior!
Another nightmare?!
What the heck!
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
Sacrifice a hen to Guliga
and things will be fine.
Is Guliga so powerful?
- Of course.
Guliga is the one who
protects our borders.
What the hell dude?
Not a single human in sight!
Only cops.
Looks like they are
searching for someone.
Shiva! Itʼs over there.
Okay.
Itʼs not working! Sh*t!
Landlord, itʼs me Shiva.
Thankfully,
everyone in the jeep survived.
We're saved!
We've to stay low in the forest
until further notice from Landlord.
Iʼll quickly go
and see my mother.
The cops are around, Shiva.
If they come, give a signal.
To whom? To the Cops or you?
Signal your dead Grandpa!
- Go home. Get some gun powder, bombs.
We will need it for hunting.
Bulla, grab some eatables
from Padmaʼs shop.
Iʼll see you soon.
- Rampa come along.
Go inside and get everything.
Shiva?!
Shiva!
I'm done with these people.
I'll leave town right away.
No fish curry today?
Thatʼs enough.
For the sins you’ve
committed, I'm starving here.
He wants fish curry!
I can't swallow anything
without fish curry.
Make it the next time I come.
Youʼre going back again?
Iʼll be back soon mother.
Not like I'm joining the Army.
Give me a Soda.
Here.
Donʼt you have any change dude?
What an opportunity
at this hour!
A cop?
If I run away now,
will you come after me?
Chanchala!
Stop right there!
Sheela, I'm here.
You guys take your time
and enjoy your food.
Iʼll wait right outside.
Please have your dinner and go.
Don't make me run.
I can't run faster.
Shiva!
Look at him eat!
The cops are here. Run!
Mother, make fish curry.
I donʼt know when Iʼll come back!
Cover him from the other side.
Run guys!
Iʼll teach those
scoundrels a lesson!
Hey Abu!
Why did you throw it?
If I light and don't throw
it, it'll explode in my hand!
You're going to get us killed.
Run!
This is what happens when
you show up at work drunk!
Are you crazy?
Sir, we didnʼt
collide with the tree.
The tree fell on us.
We didnʼt even
realise what happened.
Shut up!
You better stay away from people
like him and focus on work.
This is all Shivaʼs handiwork.
This was intentional.
Ravi, file all the
possible cases on him.
He should never see daylight.
Do you hear it too?
Yes.
Get up man!
Hey cops!
Itʼs a raid! Run!
Hey Rampanna!
Leela, the aroma is brilliant!
Are you dumb?
Why did you bring a stranger here?
Look at these street mongrels
hogging from a stranger.
Donʼt eat it idiots!
You should be lucky
to eat such food.
Bullsh*t!
My mother cooks better.
Shiva!
What a bunch of cowards!
I ran for my life
and none of you followed me.
We called you many times.
But you were too
scared to hear us.
Leela, have you come alone?
The next time you come,
please leave your anklets at home.
Did you all finish eating?
I didnʼt.
A man must be stubborn.
- Correct!
You carry on with it.
Bulla, hope you’ve left some for me.
Have it.
It's okay to be stubborn.
Not arrogant!
Done serving? Take her away.
Else Iʼll beat her to death!
Of course!
Killing people is all you know.
As if the tree incident, wasnʼt enough,
you’ve thrown bombs on the cops!
They’re searching for you
in the entire village.
In no time,
they will arrive here.
Just go to hell!
Enough eating!
Give it back!
Lacchu, come.
There was a big
piece of fish left.
She's the one who fenced her
own village on Day 1 of her job.
I donʼt trust she was
here to just give us food.
Hey Shiva!
He went off with my gun!
You may come inside,
instead of sitting like a guard outside.
We didn't intentionally
drop the tree on them.
It was an accident.
You think I did
things intentionally?
Though I wasn't at fault in the encroachment
case, you guys treated me like a dog.
Do you want a job that goes
against your own people?
Okay, Iʼll quit.
All my efforts to procure
the job will go in vain.
If it makes you
happy, Iʼll quit.
Iʼm sorry.
No need to put up an act.
Don't you see I'm apologising?
To hell with your apology.
Acting smart when I say sorry?
No Shiva.
What?
No, Shiva.
What don't you want?
You stink of beedis.
Doesn't bother me.
Remind me to offer
a hen to Guliga.
Alright.
Hey Leela!
Why didnʼt you lock the door?
What if something
dangerous enters home?
Shivanna?
- Hmm?
Where were you all this time?
I was in the forest.
I felt like seeing you all.
So, I came by.
Shivanna, in our house,
we use only grated coconut to cook.
Not the shell.
Have you eaten?
Shall we?
Come.
Shall we eat?
Dinner was good.
- I don't know who got the fish.
Howʼs my husband?
Heʼs fine.
You should have brought him too.
He didnʼt know I was coming.
Shivanna, leaving already?
Yes. I will be in
Kailasa for some time.
Go in. Have your dinner, kids.
Who told you to come here?
You could've left
without speaking a word.
Who were you trying to
inform about Kailasa?
I was telling you.
What are you thinking, Shiva?
I'll surrender.
Don't Shiva.
In a situation like this, they'll file random
cases and make sure you never get out of jail.
That's okay.
None of you should
suffer because of me.
Let’s see what happens.
Shiva!
It's dawn already. Leave now.
Go.
Hello! Good morning!
Shiva and Leela in Kailasa!
I had come up a while ago.
But I didnʼt want to disturb
since you were asleep.
The enthusiasm you had while climbing,
seems to be missing while getting down!
Off with you!
The Government pays your salary,
but you're serving him, eh?
You leave.
Donʼt you get it? Go!
I will handle these morons.
Why are you butting
in when we're talking?
Move aside!
We sure canʼt award
you for your co-operation.
But I can suspend you.
Isn’t it Shiva?
Is it loaded?
- Yes.
You have to serve
Shiva in his Kailasa.
You also have to take care of
the Landlord who got you the job.
Sir!
- Poor girl. Must be tired.
Rest for some 15 days.
Okay?
Will you hold a
torch for this too?
Itʼs Shivaʼs gun.
It's loaded sir!
Come forward!
Come.
Sir!
Move aside.
Where are you taking him?
I said move aside.
[INDISTINCT COMMOTION]
Shiva,
what happened to your face?
Forget that.
How did they catch you?
This bonehead went for a girl
but returned with the cops.
Moron!
Sorry.
- Pervert!
Obsessed with women.
Irresponsible brutes!
- Where were you?
Thought so.
As if you're
extremely responsible!
I had told him not
to leave his hideout.
His bad luck.
Good thing.
He was flying high.
Please donʼt bail him out.
If I don't do what's on my mind,
I won't be at peace, Sudhakar.
Landlord, itʼs me Guruva.
- Tell me.
Our land issues have
reached the prison.
Looks like a disaster awaits us.
You must set things
right Landlord.
Did you call at this
hour to tell me this?
Donʼt worry Guruva.
Iʼll take care of it.
What did he say?
He wants me to set things right.
No matter what happens,
everything must go right, Sudha.
In connection with the attack on forest
officers in the Kaadubettu region,
after carefully considering
the evidence presented till date
Taking IPC section 307, 353, 447, 394 and the
Forest Conservation Act 33 into account...
The permission to transfer
Shiva and his associates
to the prison as suspects
during the trial has been granted.
Take them inside.
Aren't there any women here?
- That's a different section.
Hope everything's fine.
Looks like she is still
angry with my family.
Nothing of that sort.
Please bail Shiva
and the others out.
Itʼs an attempt to murder
case on government official.
He wonʼt get bail for it.
Getting him out won't be easy.
♪ When a man stumbles
upon the stone of fate ♪
♪ Would the injury on
a finger disappear? ♪
♪ For fools who get involved under
the influence of hate and anger. ♪
♪ God doesn't wait
in the temple ♪
♪ Did the lamp meant to
light up the darkness ♪
♪ End up turning into a flame
that burnt the entire town down? ♪
You got food for me? What is it?
Itʼs fish curry.
Wow!
Why are you crying girl?
Iʼll get you ice-candy
when I come out.
Didnʼt you bring a match box?
Thanks!
Bye.
Take care.
Shivanna,
Iʼm learning to ride the bike.
Is it? Good to know.
Give it to Guruva.
Guruva, I've prayed for Shiva.
Donʼt worry about it.
Iʼm arranging for his bail.
Inform Kamala.
- Okay.
Guruva,
where are you coming from?
Itʼs Sankranthi (festival), right?
I'd gone to Bhandara mansion.
Good that I met you. Come sit.
Landlord,
how can I come with you?
Thatʼs only when others are around.
Hop in.
Did you have anything to talk about?
There are many things.
Letʼs speak as we go.
Mahadeva! Does this count
as your own courtyard?
Move aside man!
Annoying fellow!
What else Guruva?
How is your life going?
It was peaceful until now.
Youʼre well aware
of how it is now.
All will be well. Donʼt worry.
Iʼm asking only about your life.
With your meagre
earnings, are you happy?
Itʼs enough to get by.
Life is not for just getting by.
One must experience it.
Let me show you something.
Guruva, come along.
Our family owns a lot of land.
It starts from here in Kaadubettu
and spans until that hillock.
It spans over 500 acres.
I own all of this. How is it?
It's a nice place.
Guruva, youʼre serving
our Demigod sincerely.
This is my token of
gratitude for that work.
Iʼm giving you five
acres of this land.
God bless.
Do you seek anything
from me Landlord?
What will you do for me?
Come on now.
I'll drop you to Kaadubettu.
It's okay. I'll manage.
No oneʼs around.
Okay.
This is where we are.
If we take a right and go straight
from there, is the bathing area.
Now is not the time to bathe.
Damn! Be quiet.
You go on.
Take a left from there and
youʼll find the toilet.
God knows how long
he'll take to be done.
Shut up! Go on.
Thereʼs an alley next to it.
If we go straight,
thereʼs a 15-foot wall.
Each of us is at
least five foot tall.
I'm 5.5ft tall.
If we get up on each other, we'll be
able to jump over to the other side.
Freedom! Howʼs the idea?
Well done.
Who will be the last man standing?
You?
Why not? Iʼm six feet tall.
How will you jump?
Canʼt you come back and open
the gate after youʼve jumped?
Like you're father's waiting
to get you out! Dimwit!
I donʼt think you
understood what I said.
Let me explain again.
- Damn you!
This is where we are.
Let's skip this
Prison break idea.
Let's take the legal route.
We'll be fine.
All of you, go and have lunch!
This is what I love about prison.
Food's always on time.
What is this?
We were just drawing.
Who do you think
you're bluffing with?
No food for you today.
Man, you're really cursed.
You get beaten up all the time!
Hey Lacchu!
Looks like they brought back Shiva.
Where are we going?
What happened?
I donʼt know. A jeep passed by.
Thimappa, give me the matchbox.
Itʼs Guruva!
Guruva! What happened to you?
Guruva!
[CROWD WAILS]
- Brother, we lost him!
Oh god!
Guruva!
Give us poison and
kill us at once!
He's mum now.
We now have no one left!
The Landlord is entering the house.
Yeah.
Greetings Landlord!
A good-hearted soul.
He had no enemies.
Who dared to do this?
Whoever it is,
the Demigod will not spare him.
He will die vomiting blood.
Did you lodge a
complaint with the cops?
I asked to.
But theyʼre not willing to.
Why?
- He had the soul of the demi god.
Does it seem right to slash that body
under the pretext of a post-mortem?
It wonʼt just be that.
They will separate the soul
and the body and give it to us.
That body has experienced
enough pain already.
Letʼs not lodge a complaint.
At least,
let his soul rest in peace.
Letʼs inform Shiva.
If we tell him,
the cops will accompany him here.
Let the funeral rites get over.
We can inform him after that.
They mark the land thatʼs
been with us for ages.
Our kids go to jail.
A man who served the
Demigod drops dead.
What is happening here?!
Is this land cursed?
The curse can be removed.
By the time the mourning period is over,
I will destroy whoever killed Guruva.
All the village attendees!
The one who was serving the Demigod
has left to the feet of Lord Guru.
Until the another person is
appointed as the next monarch....
I shall now take out the
Guruva's symbolic attire.
♪ O'! An injured womb is a painful fate ♪
♪ Yet you wander all your
life to find a cure ♪
♪ In a conflict with
an invisible opponent ♪
♪ You shall lose yourself amidst
the task of finding oneself ♪
♪ Despite dissolving our sings, Goddess Gange
will leave you and me with repentance ♪
♪ What will you do when the fresh garland of
flower received in pride, withers away tomorrow? ♪
Kamala!
All of you are here to see me.
How are you?
Iʼm fine!
How are you all doing?
Did you go hunting?
How are you dear?
Kamala, buy her an ice-candy.
Sheʼs sobbing all the time!
I don't want you to
perform Bhoota Kola.
What?
What the hell man!
Why are you talking so strangely?
Whatʼs the matter?
Why should I perform
Bhootha Kola?
Guruva is doing it anyway.
He's doing it, right?
You will not perform the Kola.
Ever.
What happened?
- Guruva was stabbed to death.
They threw his corpse in a
jeep near the Kola arena.
Shiva!
Hey Shiva!
Murali, just 'cause the documents were
submitted, the encroachment issue won't end.
If the villagers donʼt support
you, the fight will continue.
It's not easy to convert a
forest into a reserve forest.
Drop your ego and work.
Sir, people of Kaadubettu
have replied through court.
Looks like your villagers
finally found the time.
People feel the heat only
when their as* is on fire.
Raghu, get the jeep.
- Why sir?
The scoundrel Landlord has
replied to the encroachment issue.
Devendra Suttur?
How is that possible?
Arenʼt the land owners
supposed to reply?
Letʼs find out.
- It's all over.
All the land has been transferred
to the Landlord's name.
All the documents
are now in his name.
Take care of the file.
Every time there has been survey,
that shmuck has claimed twenty acres more!
Thatʼs how his ancestors
have always been.
But we are not like that.
We have retained
the same measure.
Get the area map.
Whatʼs this?
I have to tell you something.
- What?
At one point of time, a fight broke out
putting an end to the Kola procession.
My family took over the rituals
again and we were taking care of it.
What if he gets out on bail?
- He won't.
No way.
- Really?
Only if he gets a great
lawyer, he might.
[ON CALL] Does that scammer
Devendra own so much land?
Ay! Thatʼs the area map.
A map?
Of what use is it now?
People have already
written off their land!
All documents required to convert
Kaadubettu into a reserve forest are ready.
If this file moves, the Landlord's
documents will become null and void.
Your Landlord will have to bow
down before the Lord in the Courts.
Do as you wish.
This Bhandara mansion's
Rajeeva is always with you.
Shiva should have
been with us now.
Bail out Shiva soon.
Wow! Change of mind so soon?
Didnʼt you say a while
ago not to bail him out?
Iʼm the one telling you
now to bail him out.
Is it some chicken coop to
open and release it so quickly?
Itʼs a prison!
Are you high?
Can you do it or not?
I can.
But itʼs a little tough.
If we spend some money, we can.
Iʼll speak to Subba Rao.
Hello?
Once upon a time,
there lived a king.
Just like you.
From then on, for generations,
everyone kept worshipping the stone.
When one generation
decided to reclaim the land...
Instead of shutting their traps
and taking the land back...
They decided to ask
the Demigod about it.
The Demigod...
Wait. No!
The one wearing the
Demigod's costume...
The performer told the Landlord that if he messed
with the land, he would die vomiting blood.
The Landlord realized that
it was the performer talking.
Is this the Demigod speaking?
Or is it the performer?
The performer who was caught
red-handed ran away in shame.
What happened after that?
Then the Landlord
died of old age.
The Landlordʼs son in the hope that
at least he could reclaim the land...
Come on! Let me drop you.
How can I help you Landlord?
Guruva.
I will give you some of my land.
In return, you must ensure I get
back the land I own in your village.
How is it possible, Landlord?
Eons ago, when the Demigod claimed the
land, it was given to the villagers.
From now on, Guruva must speak at the
Bhootha Kola instead of the Demigod.
Why are you talking like
this, Landlord?
Once we don the finery,
it it is the Demigod that takes over.
Nothing is in my hand
The Demigod appears
only once a while.
The rest of the time,
isnʼt it Guruva who speaks?
To satisfy your greed,
I can't speak as you desire.
The Demigod will
not appreciate this.
Itʼs not wrong to reclaim our
land, right?
Landlord!
What have you achieved by gaining
the Demigod's appreciation?
I canʼt believe
youʼre saying this.
The villagers have a
lot of respect for you.
If they get to know...
How will they know?
Will you tell them?
Will you?
Oh!
The Demigod will?
The Demigod might, right?
For the sake of that land, he dealt with the man
who was cheating us in the name of a stone.
Do you even know the
value of 100 acres?
You got it for free.
How will you know itʼs value?
I asked you to set things
right, Landlord.
I donʼt think you
realise what you've done.
If I need to set things right,
what is the use of your Demigod?
From now on,
Iʼll speak on behalf of the Demigod.
Then?
- It was a blunder.
Letʼs dispose his
body over there.
When there is plenty of
space in the forest...
Why are you keen on
disposing it there?
I have to.
For those fools who are
freeloading on my land for years...
This will serve as a warning.
After that?
Let's find out what lies next.
Okay?
People will respect us more when
we walk out of the prison, right?
We went in because
of your stupid gun!
Didnʼt you bring the axe, boy?
- No.
You should have.
Youʼve lost so much hair.
There is a plant in the forest…
A plant? Shove it up your…!
Any updates on Guruvaʼs death?
He got you out on bail.
Thank you.
I have to speak to you, Shiva.
Shiva, the Landlord
has called you home.
You donʼt have to go anywhere.
Come home.
Give me the key.
You guys come in the jeep.
Back to your old ways, you dog!
It was a mistake to get you bail!
Where are you off
to now scoundrel?
Shiva!
Shiva?
Shiva! Itʼs been so
long since I saw you!
Come. Hope things were fine in the prison.
- Yes.
I heard Rajeev bailed you out.
To get close to you I guess!
His family is known for it.
When the Bhootha Kola stopped, he took
the Demigod's ornaments to his house!
I have to speak to you.
So do I!
But first, let us party!
The Landlord always has scotch.
- What about Guddi?
Guddi drinks Landlord's scotch.
Heʼs drinking away to glory!
He doesnʼt get high easily.
Thatʼs why I gave him scotch.
He says youʼre high.
No Landlord.
I drink in buckets.
This is nothing.
I have something to ask you.
Go on.
Who killed our Guruva?
Why?
You!
You should be with us.
No matter who he is,
I will not spare him!
Iʼll kill him!
Are you done?
Send them out.
Letʼs speak in private.
You guys carry on.
Iʼll come later.
Landlord,
your crotch was superb.
Not his crotch you idiot.
His Scotch!
Devendra Suttur.
I'm a Landlord only for namesake.
But I couldnʼt serve my people.
Then why do I deserve
the title of a Landlord?
Why are you speaking
like this Landlord?
Whatʼs wrong with you?
I had a big task ahead of me
before you were released from jail.
Rajeeva got you released before that.
- Iʼm not following you.
Let me tell you this.
Donʼt lose control.
You've to listen patiently.
Do you know who
killed our Guruva?
Who?
- That son of a bi*ch DRFO!
He tried to stop
our Bhootha Kola.
When that wasnʼt possible,
he killed the performer.
He came in a jeep and threw the corpse
in the Demigod's performing arena.
Do you know how he was killed?
Shiva!
Didnʼt I tell you earlier?
You have to be patient.
Listen to me Shiva!
Donʼt act in haste. Okay?
Listen to me.
Whatever needs to be done to him,
Iʼll do it with my own hands.
This land will be
cleansed with his blood!
He killed my brother.
Why do you want
blood on your hands?
Shiva, listen to me!
Donʼt act in haste!!
Shiva!
Sudhakar, give me some water.
I just touched a rabid dog.
The tiger is off to hunt.
Once it finishes hunting,
lock it up in a cage.
Instead of killing the Forest officer,
why's he at Mahadevachari's workshop?
Mahadevanna..
Before dawn sets in,
I'll finish those who killed Guruva.
Darkness exists to give a
man's mind and body some peace.
Not to destroy it.
But it has been destroyed,
hasn't it Mahadevanna?
That son of a bi*ch DRFO!
Can the destroyer be spared?
Iʼm tugging at this for courage.
- Courage?
Courage comes from
the fire within you.
Let the fire within you
not end up burning you.
I donʼt know if it's your words or if
it's the stuff that is hitting me hard.
Your words are
passing over my head.
It is passing by.
The Landlord is taking Guruva
and is passing by in his jeep.
While returning,
the Landlord is passing by, all alone.
Later, Guruvaʼs corpse is
found in the Kola premises.
After which, the Landlord came
home to see Guruva's body.
The mystery too seems to
be passing over our head.
Take out the weapons!
- What's wrong with you?
Time to finish Shiva.
Letʼs at least ask Landlord.
By the time we do that,
Shiva will finish us off!!
Didnʼt you say that we shall
bite when the time comes?
The time has come.
Mohan, I only said that we'll bite.
Not kill.
Ay, let's go.
Mahadevanna, you have some customers
who want their swords sharpened.
Who is that?
That ember doesn't
burn in the dark.
Only this stuff will burn bright.
Come tomorrow.
But I see embers here.
Please come.
My sword is being sharpened too.
This oldie is past his prime.
Let me fire it up for you.
Donʼt fight in here.
There goes my workshop.
Iʼll get you wood
for the repairs.
Shiva!
Come to me pricks!
You mongrel!
Start the jeep!
Get in! Letʼs go.
You guys never listen to me!
Keep moving!
The Landlord is taking Guruva
and is passing by in his jeep.
They came in a jeep and threw
the corpse in the Kola premises.
Later, Guruvaʼs corpse is
found in the Kola premises.
[GURUVA WAILING]
Do you know who killed Guruva?
You!
Ammakka, hasn't the child slept yet?
- No.
Whatʼs up Shiva?
Youʼre soaking wet.
I'm not just wet, Landlord.
Iʼve been cleansed.
Wow! Looks like the squatters
have a lot to feast on.
Now that you're squatting in here too.
Join me.
Well, you walked into my house.
Why canʼt I?
Times have changed Landlord.
I can come.
Looks like you're here
to settle scores, right?
Not really!
We eat boiled rice and pickle.
Sometimes,
we can't even afford that.
Yet, we are satisfied
with what we have.
Today, Iʼm unable to
eat this fancy food.
It refuses to go down my throat.
Eat that sukka.
Ammakka cooked it. Itʼs tasty.
If one's heart is good,
everything turns out well.
Canʼt trust everything you say
now, can I?
Iʼll have to check it out myself.
Itʼs nice Ammakka.
Shiva, have some scotch.
Iʼve been cleansed, Landlord.
You have it.
What do you expect me to do now?
Havenʼt you done enough already?
Are you our Demigod to
give us what we want?
Your judgement now
lies on that land.
Whatʼs the time?
Well, looks like time
is on our side too.
It's twelve o' clock.
It's here.
Your time.
Iʼll wait for you.
Donʼt miss.
Iʼll take your leave.
Itʼs okay if you are late.
I hope you know the place.
Kaadubettu.
Greetings. Bye.
Light!
In light, everything is visible.
But this is not just light
It's a vision.
The light which will shine
on the past and the future.
Do you see it?
At least now have you people have
realised that Landlord's true colours?
What the hell!
We trusted him,
only to be brought to the streets.
We should have realised
the day Guruva dies.
When he entered our
home and shed tears.
Guddi tricked us into
meeting the Landlord!
We should take him to task!
- What meeting is this?
Are you not throwing us a party
for coming out of the prison?
The landlord is
better than you guys!
He threw us an amazing party!
- He is awesome!
What nonsense are you talking?
Kamala, are you high?
Why are you hitting me?
Why donʼt you go?
If I go, it'll only be
to my home town.
Whatʼs the use of this meeting?
We have lost our land anyway.
You can still save your land.
We have documents to declare
this land as reserve forest.
Once it is declared, both your
land and the forest will be saved.
If it is declared as forest,
how will it be our land to save?
Once the declaration happens, you
can submit a plea to the government.
The land will be handed over to the
registered owner from the time of the survey.
Our department will do the needful.
The landlord has done enough.
You please donʼt mess it up further.
Shut up! Scoundrel!
We need to stand with him.
We will. But what about Shiva?
He must be drinking at
the Landlord's house.
Looks like everyone
has united against us.
Seems like our good times
have come to an end.
Let me show you the reality.
Gather our men.
Who is he to decide my fate?
Iʼll decide his.
Has the house been
cleansed yet?!
Are you done yet?
Your moron landlord has
cheated us of our land!
It seems he listens to you.
Speak to him and
set things right!
We're talking to you.
Why are you acting like
you don't hear us?!
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Thereʼs nothing
left here for us!
The landlord has taken
over our lands completely!
He didn't just take the land.
He took Guruva too.
Grab everything you
can get your hands on!
I will take care
of that scoundrel!
Why the hell are you quiet?!
Whatʼs wrong with you?!
Letʼs barge into his house and butcher him!
Come on now!
Nobody is going anywhere.
Shiva, whatʼs on your mind?
Let bygones be bygones.
I'm sorry.
My father always told me to pay heed to the stone in
the forest, through which the Demigod will speak.
I listened to it.
The forest spoke.
Maybe if I lend my ear,
I might hear the Demigod speak too.
Our beliefs may differ Shiva,
but we are part of the same existence.
If something befalls me,
will you fight for my people?
I think heʼs here.
[INDISTINCT CRIES]
The officer is here too.
Shiva!
Iʼm glad you called me here.
Iʼm sure everyone is
aware of the matter.
Thereʼs nothing left to discuss.
How about this?
Take that stone from my
land and leave this village.
Who the hell are you to
ask us to leave our land?!
I think youʼve
forgotten who I am.
What have you done for us
to remember you any way?
Of course he has.
He cheated us of our land.
Killed my son.
Cheated us and
snatched everything...
Shut the f**k up,
you illiterates!!
If you can be this arrogant on charity
land, imagine how cocky I can get!
Is the Forest officer's presence
giving you this newfound courage?
I donʼt understand what is giving
you all this courage to blabber.
It is said that the lamp burns
its brightest before it dies.
I feel the same when I see you.
Kumara!
Have you all gone deaf?!
Heʼs speaking about
fire burning bright.
Go ahead! Burn it for him.
Burn them all!
Thrash those dogs!
Rampanna! Did the bullet
actually bounce back?!
My Grandpa's gun after all!
Heʼs one of us, Landlord.
Who cares!
I'll teach these
imbeciles a lesson.
Thinks they can come
to our home and...
Salaam Alaikum!
- Valaikum Salaam!
Ya Allah!
Landlord, thatʼs a child.
Is it yours?
If it survives, tomorrow the child
too will claim its share of land.
Take sir away to safety!
Bulla!
Die.
Throw that mongrel over here.
Koragappa! Rajeeva!
How much more you plan to fight?
Step aside.
Hold this.
Bulla!
Aye!
Come back guys.
Thatʼs enough.
Everything's done.
Shiva is dead.
Shiva!
Shiva.
My son! What happened?!
Are all of your family members here?
Only a handful of you made
it, huh?
You canʼt fool me with that useless
stone the way you fooled my ancestors.
You have two options now.
Either let go of this land
or let go of your life.
Widows donʼt have to worry.
Iʼm here for you.
Kamala, what say?!
Remember, I'll be accompanied by my
Compatriot spirit, the ferocious Guliga.
Should you err, even if I forgive
you, Guliga won't.
PROTECT US LORD GULIGA!
[IN UNISON]
Go.
Lord.
On the land of Swami Varahamurthy,
before committing any atrocities...
The one who lost the right to teach
them a lesson, on this holy land...
Did you forget the guide, Kshetrapala?
My lord Panjurli might have
forgiven, but I will not.
The result of your deeds...
By offering your
blood to this soil.
I shall safeguard its righteousness.
♪ Varaha,
the Supreme among all Gods ♪
♪ He who assumes the form of a Wild boar ♪
♪ The greatest of the Demons ♪
♪ With teeth as
hard as Diamond ♪
♪ He who protects
us like a shield ♪
♪ He who embodies the
essence of Shiva ♪
♪ The one who thrives on Earth ♪
♪ He who gives refuge to
those who believe in him ♪
♪ The one who has won the
hearts of Thousands of Gods ♪
♪ We now stand in front of
you, worshipping you ♪
Did he also disappear?